Don't worry, summer is coming.
Baywatch is a comedy, action, crime film directed by Seth Gordon.
Devoted lifeguard Mitch Buchannon butts heads with a brash new recruit.
Together, they uncover a local criminal plot that
threatens the future of the Bay.
Mitch Buchanan, played by Dwayne Johnson.
Matt Brody, played by Zac Efron.
Victoria Leeds, played by Priyanka Chopra Jonas.
Summer Quinn, played by Alexandra Daddario.
CJ Parker, played by Kelly Rohrbach.
Stephanie Holden, played by Ilfenesh Hadera.
Baywatch is a 2017 American action comedy film directed by Seth Gordon, with a screenplay by Mark Swift and
Damian Shannon, from a story by Jay Scherick, David Ronn, Thomas Lennon, and Robert Ben Garant.
It is based on the television series of the same name created by
Michael Berk, Douglas Schwartz, and Gregory J.
Bonann and takes place within the same fictional universe.
The film stars Dwayne Johnson and Zac Efron.
The story follows lifeguard Mitch Buchannon and his team, who must
take down a drug lord in an effort to save their beach.
Principal photography began on February 22, 2016,
in Florida and Savannah, Georgia.
The film premiered in Miami on May 13, 2017, and was theatrically released
in the United States on May 25, 2017 by Paramount Pictures.
It was a commercial success, grossing $177.9 million worldwide on a $65–69
million budget, but attracted negative reviews from critics.
Baywatch received five nominations at the 38th Golden Raspberry
Awards, including Worst Picture and Worst Actor for Efron.
The film explores themes of drug dealer, sea, beach, life-saver, lifeguard.
The tone is lighthearted.